<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://samuelhzx.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://samuelhzx.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-24T16:23:30+08:00</updated><id>https://samuelhzx.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Home</title><subtitle>Mathphile&apos;s personal blog </subtitle><author><name>Mathphile</name></author><entry><title type="html">a letter from Jon</title><link href="https://samuelhzx.github.io/2023/09/24/a-letter-from-Jon.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="a letter from Jon" /><published>2023-09-24T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2023-09-24T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://samuelhzx.github.io/2023/09/24/a-letter-from-Jon</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://samuelhzx.github.io/2023/09/24/a-letter-from-Jon.html"><![CDATA[<p>I saw your name in Penfriends magazine, and I would like to be your penfriend. First, I will tell you something about myself. My name is Jonathan Chen. You can call me Jon. I am twelve years old, and I am about one and a half metres tall. I have very short black hair. My hobby is playing chess.<br />
I live with my parents in the UK. They are from Shanghai. We live in a small house. My dad owns a Chinese restaurant nearby and my mum works in a college. I have a brother. His name is Willie. He is at university in London. He is studying to be an accountant. He comes back home during the holidays. How many people are there in your family? What do they do?<br />
I am in Year 7 at Walker School. It is near my house, and I can walk to school. I like my School because the teachers are very friendly. I am keen on sports. I enjoy sking and playing table tennis. My best subject is Physics. My ambition is to be an architect, or maybe an engineer.<br />
I enclosed a photo of myself and some of my school friends. I am in the middle. I also enclosed a photo of our school. It is beautiful, isn’t it? I hope you will write to me soon and tell me all about yourself.</p>]]></content><author><name>Mathphile</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I saw your name in Penfriends magazine, and I would like to be your penfriend. First, I will tell you something about myself. My name is Jonathan Chen. You can call me Jon. I am twelve years old, and I am about one and a half metres tall. I have very short black hair. My hobby is playing chess. I live with my parents in the UK. They are from Shanghai. We live in a small house. My dad owns a Chinese restaurant nearby and my mum works in a college. I have a brother. His name is Willie. He is at university in London. He is studying to be an accountant. He comes back home during the holidays. How many people are there in your family? What do they do? I am in Year 7 at Walker School. It is near my house, and I can walk to school. I like my School because the teachers are very friendly. I am keen on sports. I enjoy sking and playing table tennis. My best subject is Physics. My ambition is to be an architect, or maybe an engineer. I enclosed a photo of myself and some of my school friends. I am in the middle. I also enclosed a photo of our school. It is beautiful, isn’t it? I hope you will write to me soon and tell me all about yourself.]]></summary></entry></feed>